When she bares her claws ... You'll cringe with fear!
Ilsa, the Tigress of Siberia is a horror, thriller,
war film directed by Jean LaFleur.
Siberia 1953: Ilsa is now working in a Gulag prison camp.
Her mission is to "retrain the minds" of those who
don't agree with the communists.
Ilsa, played by Dyanne Thorne.
Michel-René Labelle, played by Michel-René Labelle.
Gregory, played by Jean-Guy Latour.
Ilsa, the Tigress of Siberia is a 1977 Canadian sexploitation "men in prison" style
film that serves as the third sequel to Ilsa, She Wolf of the SS.
The film explores themes of prison, sexploitation,
humiliation, siberia, erotic movie.
The tone is dark and intense.